Surprise!
I'm with Marta, and we are in London!
I am visiting her because she recently moved to London, and I was too excited.
I just, you know, took the first flight.
It's like the second week.
Birthe is here.
We're gonna start in Soho and have some breakfast and explore the neighborhood.
It's such a vibrant city.
London has so many amazing, inspiring people and the fashion.
So beautiful, and like, I'm immediately so fascinated by the city even though I've been here.
But it's just like now I'm older, and it's just kind of different to experience it now.
And it's just so big and so many different neighborhoods to like see.
Explore, yeah.
So we better get going.
The breakfast was really, really good.
I, of course, had egg benedicts because I love it so much, but they had egg benedicts of the day, and it was egg
florentine, and I haven't had that in a long time, and it's actually so good.
It's like spinach instead of like salmon or ham, and it's just so good.
Now I guess we're just gonna walk a bit around, check out some stores.
Maybe
I found this sweater, and I
think it's kind of cute.
It's like fussy.
I think I'm gonna try it on.
Okay, I'm not sure about like the shoulders.
They're a bit too extra for me.
I'm not sure.
Could have been cute.
It had potential.
But I'm not sure.
I'm not sure.
We checked out a few vintage stores, and Mattea
bought a reddish cardigan.
It's like burgundy red.
The color was amazing.
It was so beautiful.
But we are standing in front of a cafe called Leon, and I've seen it all over social media, and the coffee there looks
incredible.
Okay guys, this is not the ride Leon that we were planning on going to.
Switch to the ramp.
It's actually right across the street.
And this one is way more aesthetic.
The other one was like fast food.
Naturally fast food.
Yeah, but this one.
This is the one that we were looking for.
We are in Soho, and we are currently standing
on like this Danish corner.
I don't know if it's called that, but there are so many Danish designer stores here.
So it's Dinegoria, Samsø Samsø, Ganni, Han Kjøbenhavn, a lot of cool Danish stores.
Marta wants to go and check Gunny out at least, and maybe a few others.
I'm looking for some tops for when I'm going out for dinner or party.
I feel like that something that I'm missing in my wardrobe.
I found this black striped shirt, and it's a little bit more slim fitted, which I think is really nice, but I'm not sure about the silver detailing
on it.
I don't know if it's cute or if it's not cute.
So guys, I realized I totally forgot to show you our outfits, and I bought the shirt.
I think it's gonna look cute.
We are walking in a neighborhood called Marlbone.
We were checking on Google Translate how to pronounce it.
So apparently it's Marleben.
And apparently it's a beautiful neighborhood.
It's filled with cafes and cute stores.
And I checked on Google Maps if there were any bookstores because it's always fun to check out bookstores, and we found one which is so
beautiful.
So of course we need to go and check it out.
Check it out.
We are close to a bakery called Buns from Home, and their pastry looks incredible.
Like cinnamon buns, but like all kinds of flavors.
So we are going to go and taste them.
So we picked the pistachio one, and I'm very excited.
It smells amazing.
It's so crunchy.
It's kind of like a croissant in the bottom.
Yummy.
This is very good.
We are back home because we wanted to freshen up a bit, and then we are going to go out for dinner.
I kind of wanted to switch up our outfits, but before we start getting ready, I kind of wanted to show you guys what we bought because we
went to a couple of stores that I didn't really film.
I can start so in the thrift store, first one.
This is the cardigan, the red one.
Oh, maybe I can show you the color.
You can wear it, you know, over something, do like one.
All of them, or you can wear it the other way around.
So it's like a two-in-one.
Really cute.
Yeah, really, really cute.
I think it can be cute.
It suits you so well.
So actually in Budapest, Birtha showed me this.
Rare Beauty Liquid Blush.
Yeah, it's amazing.
You tried it out, and you like, you thought it was so cool.
Oh my god.
That's amazing.
Yeah, she had the color Happy.
Yeah, so we went, and I was gonna get Happy, but then we kind of decided to get like another color.
It's a bit, I think it's a bit more for me, but we got this like tester, so it's pretty.
Yeah, it's so, so cute.
I think this is gonna fit super well with your skin tone and your hair.
Exactly.
Because I'm like a blondie, and I have quite pale skin.
And this is a bit more taupe color.
Or like this.
More subtle.
Mine is a little bit more hot pink.
It's a little bit more crazy.
But this one is so, so nice.
And this is like my favorite blush ever.
It's amazing.
So I wanted to try this one.
You're gonna love it.
Oh, oh, this one is so cute.
So we went to Urban Outfitters.
Yeah, because you had seen the big selfies.
I have seen this.
Yeah.
But I don't know.
No, it's so cute.
You know, like gray gloomy days.
Oh, yeah, and you have like the black coats and stuff, and a bit of pop of color.
It's so cute.
It's like, yeah.
Yeah, and I, I mean, I didn't buy a lot.
I mean, I showed you guys earlier the shirt that I got, and it's really nice because it's just kind of like slim fitted.
Mm-hmm, and I can wear it on the night out, or I can even like wear just with jeans.
Dress it up, dress it down.
Exactly.
I have a thing for hats, I've said this many times before, and this one was on sale, and I just thought it looked cute.
This one was at Urban Outfitters.
This one was also on sale.
Yeah, we were like, it was a steal.
I think it's just a cute fit.
It's just kind of different.
Yeah.
And I love like the brushed out kind of material.
So, I think this one is gonna be cute.
Also, I don't see you with this color so much.
I'm trying to kind of expand my wardrobe with more colors.
I'm getting very inspired by Mahmood.
Yeah, because she's, like, so colorful.
Okay, and then the last one was a belt.
So this is just like a leather belt, and the buckle is also quite chunky, and it's like the perfect.
Yeah, you know, like to wear with like a dress or something.
I just, I really needed like this type of belt, so, and this was also at Urban.
Yeah, that was all that we bought.
Just wanted to do a little haul for you guys because I know you enjoy them.
So now we're just gonna do a little makeup, and then we are gonna find a nice restaurant to eat some dinner, and we are kind of in
the mood for some pasta, but we don't have a clue where to go, and I'm not sure if we're even gonna get a table
anyway, and it's Saturday night.
We're like, oh, I don't know if we're screwed, maybe, but I hope that there will be some restaurants that have like walk-ins.
Those are the best restaurants.
We're ready.
We made it out of the door, yes, and I'm wearing my new belt, and it's very cute.
So Matthew's looking slay in these pink pants and these very chunky and funky chunky shoes.
Matthew's looking good.
You too.
Good morning!
We are taking the bus to Notting Hill.
I'm so excited.
We are going to a bakery called Laila Bakery, and then we are gonna go to a market called
Portobello.
We are gonna be there at like 12ish.
We went to sleep at like 2 in the morning, so we needed a bit longer sleep.
We need our beauty rest.
And I feel like everything takes an hour to go to the mountain.
You just don't realize the lengths here are insane.
Always have to have an hour to go places.
But we're excited.
The sun is tiny bit peeking through.
It was a little bit gloomy in the morning, but now the sun is coming out.
Crossing our fingers it's gonna be sunny today.
Good day.
There is like this longest queue ever in front of Laila, and we didn't realize that it was this popular because we had plans on coming
here, and we are too stubborn.
We really want to try it like this.
It must be really good, this pastry, so we are waiting, and it's going quite fast, but we don't know if we're gonna get seats.
We'll see.
It must be good.
Yeah, it's probably worth it.
So
yeah,
Laila really exceeded our expectations.
Very good.
It was worth the wait.
Definitely, it was really good.
The pastry and the coffee especially was really, really good.
The coffee was very good.
But now we are walking towards the Portobello Market, and I think it's like antiques and some food and some clothes.
Yeah.
So we're gonna go and explore the market.
Apparently Saturday is the main day, but there are still things happening.
Yeah.
So let's see.
So we found this jewelry stand,
and I spotted this ring.
It has like an H on it, and I thought to myself, I could gift it to Helge because I think it would look cool on
him, but then I tried it on, and I think it actually looks pretty cool on my fingers, and then I always like carry him with
me, and I think it's kind of cute, so I think I'm gonna get it.
I found such a cool shirt, and it's actually Armani.
It's 75 pounds, but I think it's stunning.
So
this sweet lady just came up to us and asked us if she could do a little interview with us.
I mean, it's so fun, and I'm very flattered that she asked us, but I always get a little bit like stressed out.
I don't know, I feel like I overthink it, and somehow I just, I blank out when people ask me like questions on the spot.
This is something that I need to work on.
We said yes, of course.
She's gonna ask about our outfits, and I'm a bit like, I look a bit black today.
No, she stopped us for a reason.
She thought that we looked fashionable.
So we're gonna go and do a little interview.
Wish us good luck.
This market was actually really nice, and we ended up buying a few goodies.
There were so many cool vintage stores that have very curated pieces, but it is very expensive, to be honest.
There were a couple of pieces that we were wanting, but they were like £150 or something.
We are walking towards the Blue Door.
It's the legendary door on Notting Hill.
It's from the Notting Hill movie.
And I'm not sure if I've ever seen it with my own eyes.
So I'm very, very excited.
I love that movie.
We're
both wearing our certifines, but I think we need to go and sit down, relax for a moment.
I need to charge my phone.
It doesn't handle all the videos and all the pictures I've been taking.
Phone is just, you know, it's crashing, and it needs some power.
We are getting quite hungry, so we are gonna check if we can get a table at a restaurant that we just randomly found on Google Maps.
We're gonna see if we get a table.
Fingers crossed!
So
the restaurant turned out to be amazing.
Insane, oh, and like the flatbread that we had, it had mussels and garlic, and it was just incredible.
Good, the restaurant is a bit pricey, but it's like so good.
The food is like insane, and like all the flavors, you know, when you don't need a lot, but it's like, oh.
It was totally worth it, and I'm really happy that we decided to go there.
So I can highly, highly recommend it to you guys, and when we were about to leave, the bartender offered us shots, and we ended up taking tequila
with the bartender.
It was so funny.
Yeah, it's kind of kicking in.
Good ending.
Yeah, really good ending on a good day.
Honestly, it's been such an amazing trip to visit Mahdia.
We've had the coziest and such good quality time together.
It's been so fun exploring London.
And I'm just so in love with the city.
Like, I want to live here one day.
Yeah.
You need to come more often.
I am going to visit her, like, in a couple of months.
So I really hope you guys enjoyed watching.
And remember to go follow Mahdia.
I will have her Instagram and TikTok down below.
So thank you so much for watching, and I will see you next week.
Bye.